playnileonline.com 2011-11-24

# Immortal Cities: Nile Online » Ancient Egyptian browser-based Empire Builder

Privacy Policy 

PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. WHEN YOU USE ANY ONLINE GAME, SERVICE OR WEBSITE FROM TILTED MILL ENTERTAINMENT, INC. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS: 

Information Collection and Use 

Registration  
In order to use this website, you must first create a user name and password. During this registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and e-mail address). Tilted Mill Entertainment, Inc. (the "Company") collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on this website. Personal Information Personally identifiable information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you on-line or off-line and can include, but may not be limited to, your first and last name, home or any other physical addresses, e-mail address, phone number and other contact information. In addition we may collect demographic information such as gender, zip code, information about your computer, hardware, software, media, Internet IP addresses and connection, information about on-line activity such as feature usage, game play statistics and scores, user rankings and click paths and other data that you may provide in surveys or on-line profiles for example. We use this information: (1) to administer your account; (2) to provide information of interest to you; (3) to communicate with you in connection with contests; (4) for customer support or technical service requests; (5) for player match ups or other on-line services; (6) for registration for site membership; (7) for registration for game-specific event participation; (8) when you order products or subscriptions on-line; and (9) when you request service from third party service providers on our site. 

Usage Data  
When you play our games on your system, we may retrieve information about your hardware system and how your game is used, including your Internet Protocol Address. We use this information to enable you to play our games over the internet. We also use this information to better understand the behavior and preferences of our customers, so that we can improve our products and services. Participation in online game events is conditional upon you agreeing to us collecting, using, storing, transmitting and publicly displaying statistical data (such as your scores, rankings and achievements) generated through your participation. As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, to troubleshoot technical problems and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. In the event of user abuse of our sites, however, we may block certain IP addresses. IP addresses may be used to personally identify you to enforce our terms of service. 

Purchases  
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you. You must provide contact information (such as name and e-mail) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

No Collection of Information from Children  
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. 

Third Party Sites  
If you click on a link to a third party site, including on an advertisement, you will leave the Company site you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as the Company. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a site that is linked to the Company’s site, you should review the privacy policy before providing any personal information. 

Communications from the Company 

Service-related Announcements  
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

Customer Service  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming e-mail to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by e-mail or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. 

Profile  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files and clear gifs to create a "profile" of your preferences. We do not share your profile with other third parties. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Sharing of Information  
We do not share aggregate information (non-personally identifiable) or personally identifiable information with any third parties other than as set forth in this policy, however, in the event of merger, acquisition or bankruptcy, management of the Company’s customer information may be transferred to its successor or assign. 

Legal Disclaimer  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. 

Cookies  
We use cookies and other technologies to passively collect demographic information, personalize your experience on our site and monitor advertisements and other activities. Cookies are small files downloaded to your computer to track movements within web sites. We may link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a website. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.tiltedmill.com and www.playnileonline.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

When you visit this website, you may view advertisements posted on the site by Google or other companies. These advertising companies may collect information about you while you are visiting this site and other websites. They may use this data to show you advertisements on this site and elsewhere on the Internet about the products and services you might like. These advertisements may contain cookies. Cookies received with advertisements are collected by our ad companies and we may not have access to this information and we do not control the content of the advertisements that you will see. You may be able to opt out of the use of Google’s DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy (http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html ). Your use of this site without opting out means that you understand and agree to data collection to provide you with interest-based advertising. 

Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms  
If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. You should be aware that information you disclose on these forums in public information and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality there. 

Individuals Outside of the United States  
Please note that this website is run on a server located in the United States of America. The personal information, if any, provided by you pursuant to your registration with this site is provided to and is processed by an entity based in the United States of America. If you are a resident of another country and decide to provide personal information through this website, you acknowledge that you may not benefit from the protection of data protection laws in your country of residence. 

Access to Personally Identifiable Information  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on the Profile page of www.playnileonline.com. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our websites. 

Security  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on this website, you can email us at web@tiltedmill.com. 

Business Transitions  
In the event the Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on this website for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

Changes in this Privacy Statement  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by e-mail or by means of a notice on our home page. 

Contact Us  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at web@tiltedmill.com.
